usamega.com 2019-05-07

# Privacy Policy | USA Mega

Your privacy is a top priority and we want you to have a secure and enjoyable experience.  Any information you provide us with is kept in confidence.  The policies outlined below are applicable solely to web sites executed and run by Big Game LLC (BGL).

BGL collects personally identifying information ONLY during newsletter subscription and online sales.  BGL only uses this information to send newsletter updates and Jackpot Alerts to our guests, to process credit card transactions, and to communicate with our customers about their orders.

BGL does not sell or rent your personal information.  Unless otherwise disclosed during collection, we will not provide any personally identifying information, regardless of its source, to any third party for any purpose whatsoever.  BGL may provide aggregate statistics about our guests, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these figures will include no personally identifying information.

Guests' e-mail addresses are never posted on BGL websites, except where specifically indicated.  If you ever want to stop receiving newsletter updates or Jackpot Alerts from us, you can follow the simple instructions that appear at the bottom of each newsletter and Jackpot Alert. 

"Cookies" are small bits of information sent from a web site that are stored on your computer.  They are used to do the "record keeping" that allows a computer to remember when you've registered on a site.  This saves you the trouble of re-entering the same information during repeated visits.  BGL uses cookies only to make your experience with us easier and more enjoyable.

Your browser controls the use of cookies and, if you prefer, can be set to either accept or refuse them.  Our websites will continue to work fine on your computer without cookies, but we will be unable to provide a customized experience for you.

In conjunction with our in-house advertising, we use third-party advertising companies to place customized advertisements on the pages you view on the Site. Our third-party advertising companies also separately place or recognize a cookie file on your browser in the course of delivering advertisements to the Site. These companies may use non-personal information collected by the cookies about your visits to the Site and other web sites in order to provide you with advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

Guests under 18 years of age should not submit information to BGL without the consent of their parent or guardian. 

If you have any questions or comments regarding this statement, please contact us.
